Guide to the Grover C. Sherlin Washington Academy of Sciences (Washington, D.C.) records, 1898-2002 MS2210
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Publications, 1899-2001; Series 8
  - Proceedings, vol. 12, 1910; Series 8 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Proceedings, vol. 13, 1911; Series 8 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Index to Proceedings (vol. 1-13) and Journal (vol. 1-40), 1953; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Organization Directory, 1953-1968; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Organization Directory, 1980-1983; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 3)